<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>krei</title><link>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/</link><description>Recent content on krei</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Alternatives</title><link>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/community/alternatives/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/community/alternatives/</guid><description>In case krei is not what you are looking for, take a look at these alternatives:
krei (JavaScript) summoner (Haskell) tenzing (ClojureScript) ProjectMaker (Sublime) generate (JavaScript) yeoman (JavaScript) jeka (Java) Hazel (Swift) projector (C++) progen (JavaScript) Walter (Python) project-generator (Shell) skeletor (Shell) project-spawner (JavaScript) liftoff (Ruby) pesy (Reason) starters (R) GENie (Lua) . hygen (JavaScript) Slush (JavaScript) JHipster (Java) Comparison krei vs krei krei vs summoner krei vs tenzing krei vs ProjectMaker krei vs generate krei vs yeoman krei vs jeka krei vs Hazel krei vs projector krei vs progen krei vs Walter krei vs project-generator krei vs skeletor krei vs project-spawner krei vs liftoff krei vs pesy krei vs starters</description></item><item><title>Badges</title><link>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/metrics/badges/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/metrics/badges/</guid><description>OpenHub GitHub SonarQube</description></item><item><title>Build</title><link>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/contributors/build/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/contributors/build/</guid><description>The required build environment for krei is described in dev-env.
In case you have Java and Maven locally installed call:
# run all tests $ mvn verify # install locally $ mvn install # open jshell $ mvn --projects krei-metio --also-make --activate-profiles jshell test In case you are using ilo call this:
# build the project $ ilo @build/once # open a shell with a pre-defined build environment $ ilo @build/shell In case you want to build the website do this:</description></item><item><title>Dev Env</title><link>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/contributors/dev-env/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/contributors/dev-env/</guid><description>krei requires a certain set of software installed on your system in order to be built.
Prerequisites git for version control minisign to sign the waiver as a contributor gpg to sign your the commit which adds the waiver Manual Setup Java JDK to compile the code Maven to build the project hugo in order to create the website ilo Setup ilo to open the predefined build environment podman or docker as an ilo runtime GitHub Packages Some of krei's dependencies are only available in GitHub packages which requires authentication.</description></item><item><title>Eclipse</title><link>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/contributors/eclipse/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/contributors/eclipse/</guid><description/></item><item><title>First Timer</title><link>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/contributors/first-timer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/contributors/first-timer/</guid><description>First time contributors have to perform an additional step in order to get their changes merged into the main repository.
The WAIVER has to be signed in order to signal that all contributions can be published into the public domain using the Creative Commons Zero (CC0) license.
minisign is used to sign and verify contributions (see dev-env).
The signed waiver must be added to your first pull request. The created git commit must be GPG signed.</description></item><item><title>Git Mirrors</title><link>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/contributors/git-mirrors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/contributors/git-mirrors/</guid><description>krei is using GitHub as its primary source/issue/build environment, however its code is available in other git repositories as well in order to deal with GitHub outages.
Available Mirrors https://github.com/metio/krei https://repo.or.cz/krei.git https://codeberg.org/metio.wtf/krei https://gitlab.com/metio.wtf/krei https://bitbucket.org/metio-wtf/krei Automatic Mirroring The Gitlab repository pulls changes from GitHub and pushes changes into Codeberg and Bitbucket. The repo.or.cz mirror pulls from GitHub as well, therefore all you have to do is, push your changes into GitHub and a few minutes later, all other repositories will get the latest code automatically - including all branches.</description></item><item><title>Help</title><link>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/community/help/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/community/help/</guid><description>In case you need help, don’t panic - we’ve all been there! Try the following resources in order to get help:
open a new bug report create a new feature request join the chat room send an email to the mailing list ask on stackoverflow Take a walk outside &amp;amp; come back to your issue with a fresh mind</description></item><item><title>Install</title><link>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/krei-core/install/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/krei-core/install/</guid><description>In order to use krei-core in your project, add it as a dependency. You can find all published versions either at GitHub or Maven Central
Maven &amp;lt;dependency&amp;gt; &amp;lt;groupId&amp;gt;wtf.metio.krei&amp;lt;/groupId&amp;gt; &amp;lt;artifactId&amp;gt;krei-core&amp;lt;/artifactId&amp;gt; &amp;lt;version&amp;gt;KREI_VERSION&amp;lt;/version&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/dependency&amp;gt; Replace KREI_VERSION with the latest available version in either GitHub or Maven Central.</description></item><item><title>IntelliJ Idea</title><link>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/contributors/idea/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/contributors/idea/</guid><description>IntelliJ Idea is a popular IDE by Jetbrains. It allows several ways to share settings across team members in a project.
krei stores its IntelliJ settings inside its git repository and thus should work out-of-the-box for other IntelliJ users.
In case you have trouble getting krei to work in IntelliJ, take a look at the help section.</description></item><item><title>JShell</title><link>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/krei-core/jshell/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/krei-core/jshell/</guid><description/></item><item><title>License</title><link>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/krei-core/license/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/krei-core/license/</guid><description>krei can manage the license for your projects.
Declarative API Standard Configuration import wtf.metio.krei.model.license.License; import wtf.metio.krei.template.LicenseTemplates; var projectName = &amp;#34;your-project&amp;#34;; var license = License.of(LicenseTemplates.CC0, projectName); configure LICENSE file configure AUTHORS/WAIVER file configure source file header configure README license section use provided project name for templating Custom Configuration import wtf.metio.krei.model.license.License; import wtf.metio.krei.model.license.Waiver; import java.nio.file.Paths; var projectName = &amp;#34;your-project&amp;#34;; var license = License.builder() .license(&amp;#34;your license text&amp;#34;) .licenseFile(Paths.get(&amp;#34;/path/to/the/LICENSE/file&amp;#34;)) .sourceHeader(&amp;#34;your source file header&amp;#34;) .</description></item><item><title>Makefile</title><link>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/contributors/makefile/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/contributors/makefile/</guid><description>The Makefile commonly used task by maintainers of this project. In order to use it, you have to install a variant of make on your system. Just calling make in the root directory will print the help/usage guide:
$ make usage: make [target] contributing: sync-mirrors Synchronize changes to all git mirrors sign-waiver Sign the WAIVER hacking: install Install all artifacts into local repository verify Verify all modules site Build website site-watch Build and watch website build-env Open a new shell in a predefined build environment build-once Build the entire project once in a predefined build environment jshell Open project in a JShell other: help Show this help Run any of the available targets like this:</description></item><item><title>Maven</title><link>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/krei-metio/maven/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/krei-metio/maven/</guid><description>All Maven projects at https://github.com/metio adhere to a certain project setup/layout which includes:
Use Creative Commons Zero license Create LICENSE Create AUTHORS/WAIVER Create README.md Create CODE_OF_CONDUCT.md Create CONTRIBUTING.md Create CHANGELOG.md Create .github/SECURITY.md Create .github/SUPPORT.md Create templates in .github/ISSUE_TEMPLATE/ Create .github/ISSUE_TEMPLATE/config.yml Create templates in .github/PULL_REQUEST_TEMPLATE/ Create .github/workflows/release.yml Create Makefile Create pom.xml Use maven-build-process as Maven parent Configure IntelliJ Idea code style settings Configure IntelliJ Idea copyright settings Create docs folder with metio-hugo-theme as theme Initialize Git repository Setup local Git configuration Create .</description></item><item><title>Metadata</title><link>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/contributors/metadata/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/contributors/metadata/</guid><description>Every contributor may add/remove her/his metadata to the list of contributors at any time.
Metadata is currently used in three places:
To generate a list of existing minisign signatures in the first timer documentation. To generate a humans.txt file of all contributors. To generate a FOAF for the entire project. Adding a new entry Create a new file called &amp;lt;YOUR_NAME&amp;gt;.yaml in the contributors directory. Add the following properties to it:</description></item><item><title>News</title><link>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/community/news/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/community/news/</guid><description>In order to stay up-to-date, consider the following resources:
Join the chat room Join the mailing list Join the reddit community Subscribe to the release feed</description></item><item><title>Release</title><link>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/contributors/release/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/contributors/release/</guid><description>The release process of krei is highly automated, therefore you only have to:
Push changes into the master branch Wait until an GitHub action will perform a release automatically Each new release will:
Publish a new GitHub release Publish an email Publish a toot</description></item><item><title>Security</title><link>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/community/security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/community/security/</guid><description>Supported Versions krei is using a continuous delivery mode and therefore only supports the latest released version.
Reporting a Vulnerability Email security@metio.wtf with details about the vulnerability.
Please include some way to reproduce your problem. We are going to provide a fix as soon as possible and include it in the next release.</description></item><item><title>static-void-main</title><link>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/krei-core/main/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/krei-core/main/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Usage</title><link>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/krei-core/usage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/krei-core/usage/</guid><description>In order to create a new project with krei you will have to follow these steps:
Define a project: Create a Project or ProjectConfiguration Generate a project: Materialize the above definition to the file system Validate a project: (Optional) validate definition against best-practices and check generated project against definition. Celebrate \o/ Define Projects krei-core offers a high-level declarative API and a low-level imperative API.
Declarative API The main interface of the declarative API is ProjectConfiguration.</description></item></channel></rss>