<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Community on krei</title><link>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/categories/community/</link><description>Recent content in Community on krei</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/categories/community/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Alternatives</title><link>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/community/alternatives/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/community/alternatives/</guid><description>In case krei is not what you are looking for, take a look at these alternatives:
krei (JavaScript) summoner (Haskell) tenzing (ClojureScript) ProjectMaker (Sublime) generate (JavaScript) yeoman (JavaScript) jeka (Java) Hazel (Swift) projector (C++) progen (JavaScript) Walter (Python) project-generator (Shell) skeletor (Shell) project-spawner (JavaScript) liftoff (Ruby) pesy (Reason) starters (R) GENie (Lua) . hygen (JavaScript) Slush (JavaScript) JHipster (Java) Comparison krei vs krei krei vs summoner krei vs tenzing krei vs ProjectMaker krei vs generate krei vs yeoman krei vs jeka krei vs Hazel krei vs projector krei vs progen krei vs Walter krei vs project-generator krei vs skeletor krei vs project-spawner krei vs liftoff krei vs pesy krei vs starters</description></item><item><title>Help</title><link>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/community/help/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/community/help/</guid><description>In case you need help, don’t panic - we’ve all been there! Try the following resources in order to get help:
open a new bug report create a new feature request join the chat room send an email to the mailing list ask on stackoverflow Take a walk outside &amp;amp; come back to your issue with a fresh mind</description></item><item><title>News</title><link>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/community/news/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/community/news/</guid><description>In order to stay up-to-date, consider the following resources:
Join the chat room Join the mailing list Join the reddit community Subscribe to the release feed</description></item><item><title>Security</title><link>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/community/security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://krei.projects.metio.wtf/community/security/</guid><description>Supported Versions krei is using a continuous delivery mode and therefore only supports the latest released version.
Reporting a Vulnerability Email security@metio.wtf with details about the vulnerability.
Please include some way to reproduce your problem. We are going to provide a fix as soon as possible and include it in the next release.</description></item></channel></rss>